Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi. A
few times when I went live on it, many
people asked me this question that
everyone understands what you eat, but we
need homework and we have to do it ourselves
and similarly I got a lot of comments
on the videos and many people also
wrote to me on email at alarmbirthdaykedarjadav@gmail.com so the problem was that I will
give you those things but how will I check that
clash it is not possible for
me or the media to check everyone so what will we do now
see we
cannot make exercises on every episode but you will shine
what about the episodes
we are taking a test of 100 on the first 5 episodes today
and we will make a test series it is not like that for every 5 episodes
sometimes the
winner will be selected by turning off the important episode mode so there will be 10
questions on it and another test will be made for 2 or 3
episodes only and it will be
written in that category
which episodes will be selected on it so there will be three
benefits of it  The first trap, if you are going to learn from the beginning, then
what I will do is I will put this episode
in that plate in such a place that
after you watch the first 5 episodes, then you will know whether
I can go ahead or not,
if you understand that all the characters are similar then you
can go to Papa, secondly, there are many of you
who are already learning, for them you have to
revise, that is, I will
start with the special one, then you can do this
cricket test series again and start doing it,
I am going to make a separate playlist for it,
first, okay, the first test is over, the second
test is over, it is a little more difficult than your third test,
so start the questions from there,
come, many people have
also written to me in the comments on email that you have
studied * somewhere else, but you do not know how to
learn it here, you can study in the next part, what can you do, you will
start cleaning the table, when you feel that I do
not know beyond this, you start studying from there,
many people do not like this, it has many
benefits, so let's start, so today we are going to
take the first 5 episodes of Purple
Twenty  Five question test so let's
start right now you must be seeing these questions on the screen right now there might be
some mistakes in my Hindi so I have given them in English
also you can call I would request you all
to pause this first
solve it with pen and paper and when it is completely solved then only
you can proceed from here do
not cheat as much as possible reminder of March it is really important for you to
know whether you have reached the
top or not consist completely
okay I hope you all must have done this
third question let's all answer together
and they say that also see so
first 5 is easy first episode
make your small sentences I drink tea do
this cream second you play cricket
far pins went behind she lives in Pune we want in we have that
pan Shweta air length
water we eat pizza khayatana pizza
and they participate so you can do this here
river is unique so in the middle in Hisar
okay right now do some numbers we mean
this is not to my limit so you  838 hard work like
these women a little unit is not strange 309641
service
was 367th which seems hard for the
youth to do rate a little bit Munter life
objective and in the end more than 90 have to do
9th Ujjain Rai Kundal Sworn in that I have a
little havan thank you
that he is Anil exit Anil after that there is a little that if you have done it
well here then
WeChat period you have force groom
posture if you have added taste 1 nutrition
they are students different students 10 and now a little bit of
my introduction now let's talk
I am character this Vin Kedar I
live in Munich this he is nine eyes
I speak English this pressure English I am
36 years old this Vin the Sun Rise Gaya Nal
I have come from India this is mouse
Indian we do a little bit golden words right now I do
n't know how much in Hindi but if you
ask for Shubh Prabha then nowadays we say Good Morning then
he is saying U-Turn Morgan Namaste
or Hello so if you  If you want to
ask how I am doing
on those planets, then it will be the weekend.
If you want to say thank you to everyone, then it will be the
dank. If you put that and then
surround the egg, there are many, then
tell me and if you want to say goodbye to someone, it will be bye.
If I was saying a for money,
now Twitter Dahan and if you are saying it to a friend, then
Shiv, I hope that all of you are doing
well and must have checked all
your masks and hence you
can write it down so that I can know where you
are. The next ad mark is in the material. You can
understand where I am. If you will see
25 stars today, hence a mistake has happened, then
your first episode is over
now, you can move ahead. We will keep doing this with every test.
This test series will continue like this.
I hope you liked this episode,
we will meet
in the next episode. Thank you.